That's nice...
いいですねぇ...
Hey...
ねぇ...
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Why are you nervous?
何で緊張してるの?
After having sex?
エッチした後だから?
Yes, after we had sex?
うん エッチした後だから?
Just a little...
ちょっとね...
Just now...
さっきね...
Because I had sex...
エッチしちゃったからね...
how was it?
どうだった?
Oh, did you eat it?
あ、食った?
It's just too cute that I can't resist...
ちょっと我慢できずに可愛すぎて...
a little bit...
ちょっと...
I did it...
やっちゃいました...
I'm getting sleepy...
眠くなっちゃうでね...
After having sex...
エッチした後ね...
Cute...Idol type...
可愛い...アイドル系だね...
I like this yukata...
いいね、この浴衣ね...
I've been watching a lot lately, but this...
最近めっちゃ見るんだけど、これさ...
What happened today?
なに、今日あれなの?
Are you wearing something amazing?
すごい着てんの?
A cherry blossom viewing event...
花見大会って...
a...
あ...
That's right, isn't it?
そうだよね
...
I see this a lot...
この...めっちゃ見るんだけど、
this...
この...
Well, something...
さ ぁ、なんか...
Did you buy it yourself?
自分で買ったの?
scene...
シーン...
I guess it's popular...
人気なんだろう...
There's a lot in the rear that looks like it's going to be worn a lot.
結構着るっぽいリアにいっぱい
...
She was a little too cute so I called out to her...
ちょっと 可愛すぎて声かけちゃいましたけど...
What do you usually do?
普段は?
What are you doing?
何してるんだっけ?
Are you a student?
学生だっけ?
university student?
大学生?
Women's college...
女子大...
Is that so?
そうなの?
Women's college?
女子大?
Are there only girls?
女子しかいない?
There are only girls...
女子しかいない...
By the way, where is it...
ちなみにどこだよな...
Tea drinking water...
お茶飲み水...
Why is that...
なんでそんな...
Smart...
頭いい...
It's supposed to be...
はずなのに...
Stop calling me stupid...
バカンっぽく言うのやめても...
Ah, that's right...it's a women's university...
あ、そうなんだ...女子大なんだ...
No boys?
男子いない?
not present...
いない...
I want to enter...
入りたい...
Can I come in?
入っていい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Are you okay...
大丈夫...
Is your boyfriend okay?
彼氏いいの?
I'm not there...
いないです...
Mother and child middle school?
母子中?
Even though it's so cute...
こんな可愛いのに...
How many people have you dated so far?
今まで何人と付き合ったことある?
Alone...
一人...
Alone?
一人?
That's right...
そうなんだ...
when?
いつ?
That's right...
そうなんだ...
By the way, the number of people with experience...
ちなみに経験人数とか...
Alone...
一人...
amazing...
すごい...
High school?
高校の?
Karepi?
カレピ?
Nice...
いいな...
Only one person has done it...
一人しかしてないんだ...
How many times did you do it?
何回もした?
fault...
あら...
You seem to like naughty things...
エッチだって好きそうだね...
She had a very erotic body...
すごいエロい体をしてた...
Do you not have sex with anyone other than your boyfriend?
彼氏以外とエッチしない?
Why not...
しないか...
It's a women's university...
女子大だしね...
What's up with your part-time job?
バイトどうかしてます?
welcome...
いらっしゃいませ...
Nice to meet you...
だいたいいらっしゃいませ...
almost...
だいたい...
Where are you welcome...
どこのいらっしゃいませ...
It's Missed...
ミスドです...
Misdo...
ミスド...
I'm sure you're welcome...
確かにいらっしゃいませ...
Missed recently...
ミスドも最近...
something...
何 か...
You want to eat it...
食べたいんだよね...
Motchurin is over...
モッチュリンは終わった...
I want to eat mochulin...
モッチュリン食べたい...
It'll sell out quickly...
すぐ売り切れるんだよね...
If you line up at 10 o'clock and 10 o'clock...
10時と22時に並べば...
You can buy...
買えます...
I can't buy it...
買えないんだよ...
Even if you line up...
並んでも...
I will do my best...
頑張ります...
Make it special...
作ってよ、特別に...
That's impossible...
無理ね...
Please...
頼むよ...
I can only raise...
レイズしかできない...
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
I haven't made it
作ってないんだ
...
We had sex a little while ago...
もう ちょっとさっきエッチしたから...
This bottom...
この下がさ...
It's soft, isn't it?
柔らかいよね
...
Look, it's out...
ほ ら、出てきました...
Try it...
ベーってしてみて...
It feels super good, but...
超気持ちいいんだけど...
A kiss...
キスが...
Why does it feel good?
なんで気持ちいいの?
That's terrible, bottom...
やばいね、下...
Just now...
さっきさ...
These too...
これらも...
I had it done, but...
してもらったけどさ...
Behind...
後ろに...
I'm behind...
後ろに来ました...
Hello ...
こんにちは ...
Ah, hello...
あ、こんにちは...
Mocchurin, please...
もっちゅりん、ください...
You're popular, right?
モテるでしょ?
It doesn't come out...
出ない...
I wonder if it won't come out...
出ないことはないか...
Not many boys...
あんまり男子と...
Don't you have a chance to meet them?
接する機会がないのかな?
I ignore it, but I ignore it...
無視するけど、無視する...
Ignore?
無視する?
What would you do if you were a really cool person?
めっちゃかっこいい人だったらどうする?
Follow me, this...
ついてくね、これね...
It depends on the person, I guess...
人によるよね、そんなのね...
That's right...
そりゃそうだ...
Of course, underwear...
当然下着はね...
Put it on, okay?
つけてよ、ね...
I was a little naked earlier.
さっきはちょっと裸に
...
Good, press the screen...
いい ね、画面押しに...
You've never been photographed like this, have you?
こう やって撮られたことはないでしょ?
Is there one?
あるんだっけ?
do not have...
ない...
Isn't that what it is?
なんか、あれじゃない?
Ex-boyfriend...
元彼...
With my ex-boyfriend...
元彼と...
Did you go where you took the photo with your ex-boyfriend?
元彼と撮ったとこ行ってなかった?
some time ago
さっき
...
That's right, it's a kimono.
そうだ よね、着物だからね
...
I had sex with my ex-boyfriend...
元 彼とエッチしてさ...
Since then...
以来はさ...
I didn't have a chance to have sex...
エッチする機会がなかった...
Until now?
今に至るまで?
do not have ...
ない ...
So it's been over a year?
じゃあもう1年以上とか?
Really?
本当に?
Alone, like this...
一人でさ、こうなんか...
Do you know the owner?
オーナーに行って知ってます?
I know...
知ってます...
Have you been to the owner?
オーナーに行ったことある?
oh dear...
まあ...
That's why...
そういうので...
Well, I guess it's resolved...
まあ解消かな...
Like...feeling?
みたい な...感じ?
Well, that's right...
まあそうだよね...
Eh, below this...
え、これ下はさ...
Seriously, don't watch this often...
マジでこれよく見るな...
What, is it famous?
な、有名なの?
This is a kimono...
これ、着物...
It's selling
売れてるんだ
...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Ah, it's black, the bottom too...
あ、 黒だね、下も...
Is there a lot of black?
黒が多いの?
Not many...
多くない...
Suddenly today...
今日は突然...
I was brought...
連れてこられた...
Because you brought me...
俺に連れてこられたから...
I haven't decided...like...
決めてない...みたいな...
It's cute, but...
かわいいよ、でも...
Were the fireworks beautiful?
花火綺麗だった?
It feels like boom...
ドーンって感じ...
Did you see it locally?
現地で見たの?
Right?
だよね?
Are there too many people?
人多すぎない?
Were you watching from a distant building?
遠くのビルから見てたの?
I have a house...
家がある...
From a little distance away?
ちょっと離れたところから?
Might be cute...
かわいいかも...
You think I’m cute, right?
私、かわいいと思うでしょ?
I'm the cutest in the world...
私が世界で一番かわいいよね...
I really think so...
本当にそう思ってる...
You're doing it behind my back too...
後ろでもしてるね...
Me...
自分ね...
It's white, your skin...
白いね、肌ね...
Nothing is burnt
何にも焼けてないね
...
A man's skin...
男 の人に肌か...
You can also see...
見られるのも...
It's been a long time...I mean...
久々...ってことだよね...
Really?
本当に?
I guess she has about 5 boyfriends?
彼氏5人くらいいるんじゃない?
Lots of hooks...
フックがいっぱい...
There's a lot of this...
いっぱいあるね、これ...
It's one of many patterns...
いっぱいあるパターンのやつだね...
I'm embarrassed...
恥ずかしながら...
Maybe two...
2つとかね...
I could do something like that, but...
そういうのもいけるんだけど...
With one hand...
片手でこう...
There's only one left...
あと1個だ...
I wonder if I can go...
いけるかな...
Ah, no...
あ、いけない...
There's only one more...
あと1個なんだけど...
It's a bit scary...
ちょっとなんかやばい...
Like a virgin...
童貞みたいな...
difficult...
難しい...
Take it...
取って...
Can you show me?
見せてくれる?
It sank...
沈んだ...
You were jumping up and down earlier...
さっき飛び跳ねてたよね...
Did you get it?
取れた?
I got it...
取れました...
Well...
じゃあ ...
May I see it?
見せていただいてもいいですか?
So cute...
か わいいな...
It's getting closer...
近づいちゃう...
cute
かわいい
...
I wonder how much it will cost...
ど んな足するんだろう...
what happened?
どうしたの?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
delicious?
おいしい?
Something...
なんか ...
It tastes like lavender...
ラベンダーの味がする...
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
It feels like...
って感じに...
Can you feel my nipples?
乳首感じるの?
what?
な に?
Are you sensitive?
敏感なの?
Do you touch it yourself?
自分で触ったりする?
a little bit?
ちょっと?
Is that so?
そうなの?
By yourself?
自分で?
Some kids don't feel it at all...
全然感じない子もいるから...
That's amazing...
それはすごい...
That's a good thing...
いいことだよね...
That's what I heard
と こだよ
...
Isn't it here too?
ここ もあるんでしょ?
By myself...
自分で...
certainly
当然
...
came out
出 てきた
...
There are etching stains...
エ ッチャーシミがついてる...
Etcher stain...
エッチャーシミが...
Can I take this home?
これ持って帰っていい?
I want a new one...
新しいの欲しい...
Bubbly exchange?
ブツブツ交換?
You're exchanging it for mine...
俺のと交換してるじゃん...
It's like exchanging uniforms...
ユニフォーム交換みたいな...
You have a beautiful body...
綺麗な体してるね...
I can't believe it's so cool...
まさか超カッコよくしてる...
It's beautiful...
綺麗じゃん...
Take your time...
じっくりね...
With my own hands...
自分の両手でさ...
It's par
パーってさ
...
Firmly...
し っかりと...
You can see inside...
中まで見える...
You've never dressed like this, have you?
こんな格好したことないでしょ?
I agree...
そうだ ね...
You look at it a lot, right?
めっちゃ見るでしょ?
Yeah...
うん...
Because I like it...
好きだから...
yeah?
ん?
What are you doing?
何してんの?
It's really shocking...
すごいビックビックするね...
You're sensitive...
敏感だね...
chestnut?
くり?
Have you ever been licked?
舐められたことあるでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気持ちいいの?
Are you doing it yourself?
自分でやってるとこ?
Yeah ...
うん ...
Go to sleep, don't sleep...
寝る寝るなって...
It's getting really wet...
すごいぬるくなってきた...
Something came out...
なんか出てきたね...
I'm getting soaked...
ビチョビチョになっちゃう...
What came out now?
何出てきたの今?
Your butt is getting wet.
お尻が濡れちゃってるね
...
It's a really nice kit
め っちゃいいキットしてる
...
Bichobicho...that's terrible...
ビ チョビチョ...やばいね...
I feel good.
気 持 ち いいしてるな
...
Is it cute?
か わいいね
...
If you sleep properly...
ちゃん と寝たら...
yeah?
ん?
what?
何ですか?
It's like...
みたいな感じ...
This bed is amazing
すごいよこのベッド
...
water bed
ウ ォーターベッド
...
It's a long touch...
触 りが長いよね...
Tingling...
ツンツンして...
That's terrible...the way you touch it...
やばいね...触り方...
good?
いい?
Even this is a little scary...
これでもちょっとやばいわ...
amazing...
すごい...
amazing ...
すごい ...
Where I'm licking...
ペロペロしてる先...
mask...
マスク...
If you look at it from a distance...
遠くから見たら...
surely
確かに
...
That's amazing...
すごい 下だね...
すごいよ...
under hair
髪の下
...
Good face
いい 顔するね
...
amazing...
すごい...
It's crunchy...
コ リコリするね...
Back...
奥...
Here is
ここが
...
I'm holding your leg...
足 抱えてるの...
it is...
それは...
That's a bit dangerous...
それはちょっとやばいやつ...
The sound of water...
水の音...
That's amazing...
すごいね...
You can move really well
すごい動けるね
...
amazing...
すごい...
That feels good
それ気持ちいい
...
That's amazing...
すごい ね...
Move, move...
動いて動いて...
Is it okay to take it slow?
ゆっくりでいいかな
...
terrible
や ばい
...
That's amazing
すごい ね
...
Peropero...
ペ ロペロ...
TRUE
本当
To?
に?
long time no see?
久 しぶり?
It’s been a while
久しぶ
Because...
り だから...
amazing...
すごい...
A little more...
あともうちょっと...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Let's hit the limit 4 times...
限界4回出そう...
Come here...
こっち来て...
I wonder if he's holding his legs...
足抱えてるかな...
by hand
手で
...
I'm going...
行 っちゃうよ...
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Let me out...
出してよ...
Really let it out
本当に出してよ
...
It's here...
ここ あるよ...
or
や
It happened
っちゃ ったね
...
As expected...
さ すがにもう...
You're exhausted...
くたくたでしょ...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
amazing...
すごい...
That's amazing...
すごいさ...
I'm here again, Yukata...
また来ちゃったんだ、浴衣...
amazing...
すごい...
That's it...
あれだね...
licking...
ペロペロ...
I guess I can't get it across...
伝わらないかな...
Is there a huge amount of air?
大気量がすごいのかな
...
amazing...
すごい...
I just put it out...
ちょっと出したばっかりなのに...
Even though it just came out...
出したばっかりなのに...
Pick...
ピックに...
Pick magnum...
ピックマグナムに...
What should I do...
どうしよう...
Pick Magnum...
ピックマグナム...
pick...
ピック...
Pick mug?
ピックマグ?
Very tight
すごい締まり
...
It's so tough
すごい きついんだ
But...
けど...
what happened?
どうしたの?
Amazing touch...
すごい触り方...
Touch like a technician...
テクニシャンみたいな触り方...
technician?
テクニシャン?
Aren't you a technician?
テクニシャンじゃないの?
There's a lot in there.
すごい入ってるね
...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just a little over here
もう ちょっとこっち
...
Good, good.
いい よいいよ
...
Can you do that?
そんな できるの?
そんなできるの?
amazing...
すごい...
Can you move like that?
そんな動けるの?
by yourself
自分で
...
That's amazing
すごい ね
...
cute...
か わいい...
wait a minute ...
ちょっと 待って ...
wait a minute...
ちょっと待って...
Posture...
体勢や...
I wonder what this is
これなんだろうね
...
One last thing...
ちょっと 最後にさ...
a little bit...
ちょっと...
The taste of cloth...
布の味...
Behind...
後ろにさ...
Get your hands on it...
手ついてごらん...
Look at your legs hanging down...
足垂れてごらん...
Move a little slowly...
ちょっとゆっくり動いて...
That's amazing
すごいね
...
amazing...
すごい...
Yaba
やば
...
Elleke...
エ ルレケ...
It's called Elleke.
エルレケってしてるね
...
amazing...
すごい...
terrible...
やばい...
terrible
やばい
...
a little bit...
ちょっと...
I'll put it out again
また出しちゃうよ
...
Looks like I can stand it...
立 てなせそう...
I put it out again...
また出しちゃったよ...
a little bit ...
ちょっと ...
I did it earlier too...
さっきもしたのに...
Because it's erotic...
エロいから...
What were you thinking of doing?
どうしようと思ったの?
It's always been like that...
ずっとそんな感じじゃん...
Troublesome...
めんどい...
sleepy...
眠たい...
how was it?
どうだった?
So...
めっちゃ...
It felt good...
気持ちよかった...
Which body do you like?
どの体が好きなの?
Wack...
ワック...
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
sleepy?
眠い?
Are you getting sleepy?
眠くなっちゃうの?
After having sex...
エッチした後...
real...
ほんと...
Any other thoughts?
他に感想あります?
sleepy...
眠い...
That's good...
よかったってことね...
good...
よかった...